<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Change log of Android App 15.0 . Keep the dash character (-) and line breaks to keep the list format. -->
    <string name="android_change_log_v15_0">- Set up one-way sync to back up specific device folders to your cloud seamlessly.\n- The document scanner now offers better accuracy, faster scans, enhanced editing, and improved edge detection.\n- Add photos to albums directly from Cloud Drive for easier organisation.\n- A new colour palette improves navigation clarity and makes the app more intuitive and enjoyable.</string>
    <!-- Change log of Android App 15.14 . Keep the dash character (-) and line breaks to keep the list format. -->
    <string name="android_change_log_v15_14">- You can now edit photos. Crop, rotate, and scale, or adjust brightness, contrast, and more.\n- It’s now possible to set sync preferences based on your connection or power source, like Wi-Fi vs mobile data, or charging vs battery.\n- The audio player now supports playback position history. If you previously played more than 15 minutes of a file, you’ll be asked whether to resume or start over.\n- We’ve fixed bugs and improved performance and reliability.</string>
    <!-- Change log of Android App 15.15 . Keep the dash character (-) and line breaks to keep the list format. -->
    <string name="android_change_log_v15_15">- You can now resolve multiple sync issues at once with the new bulk fix option.\n- Bugs have been fixed and performance improved.</string>
    <!-- Change log of Android App 15.16 . Keep the dash character (-) and line breaks to keep the list format. -->
    <string name="android_change_log_v15_16">- Folders now take on the colour of their label for easier organisation and quicker access.\n- Stability has been improved and bugs resolved.</string>
    <string name="android_change_log_v15_17">- New: Hidden files and folders. Keep private or sensitive data out of sight, without needing to delete or move anything.\n - Chats and meetings can now be searched using the email addresses of the participants.\n- Bugs have been resolved and the overall app performance improved.</string>
</resources>